Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Arts and Media Serials TAM.772
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Weimarer Beitrage: Aufbau - Verlag, Berlin, Germany, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Westchester Artsnews: Council for the Arts in Westchester, White Plains, NY, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- What Are You Going to Do About It?: Chicago Surrealist Group, Evanston, IL, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Whirl: El Estudio Press, Santa Fe, NM, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Wireless: WEFT 90.1 FM Program Guide: WEFT / Prairie Air, Champaign, IL, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Witness: Witness Publishers, Inc., Farmington Hills, MI, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Women & Film: Women & Film, Santa Monica, CA, 1972-1975 (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
- Women and Art Supplement on Art and Society: Women and Art Supplement, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- World's Word: World's Word, Washington, DC, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Writer's Monthly: Writer's Monthly, Springfield, MA, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Yellow Springs Review: Yellow Springs Institute, Chester Springs, PA, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Zamlungen: A Literary Quarterly: Jewish Writers Organization of the YKUF, New York, NY, 1954-1977 (Box 15, Folder 12, Box 16, Folder 1-6, Box 17)
- Литературная газета: орган Правления Союза советских писателей СССР (Literary Gazette: Board of the Union of Soviet Writers of the USSR): Тип. Гудок Moskva: Tip. Gudok, Russia, 1956 (Box Shared Tamiment 048, Folder 13)